Traffic Safety
with
Doraemon
Original Creator:
Fujiko. F. Fujio
Production:
Shogakukan
I'm home!
Welcome home!
Where are you going to?
To play!
And when will you do your homework?
Later!
Our playground...
Construction Ongoing
Trucks go here
The construction has begun already!
Build what?
A huge mansion is going to be built here.
So we can't play here anymore!
Too bad!
Kids, go home! It's dangerous here!
Come on...
Can I open my eyes?
Not yet!
Can I open my eyes now?
You can!
She won't find me here!
Ah! Found you, Nobita-kun!
We can't really play hide and seek here in the road!
Nobita!
Then let's switch our places.
Let's play catch-ball!
Come on! We came here first!
You got a problem with that? You jerk...!
Enough!
How dare you!
Stop!
What's up?
I fled from Giant!
Oh, the usual fight?
What a mean thing for you to say that, Doraemon!
An accident, huh?
Giant's late again!
Before I start taking roll no.
I have a sad news for all of you.
Gouda Takeshi-kun had an accident yesterday and he's been now hospitalised.
What?
Around what time?
Around 5:00 PM at the flowershop near your house.
Oh no!
I was fleeing from Giant then...
Don't tell me that he...
Say what? Giant had an accident yesterday when he was chasing you?
Yes, sadly.
What now, Doraemon?
Let's go visit him in the hospital!
Giant, there's no need to hide your face.
It's totally uncool of me to show my face to you all.
I don't care weather you're acting cool at a time like this.
I beg of you, please leave!
Giant, we're but your friends, so please show us your face.
Get out!
An accident? A girl's doll had an accident it seems. She was crying and all.
What? A doll?
But it should be a fat boy!
No, A doll! I'm sure of it!
Come on!
That's all I know, about an accident.
It's totally confusing!
Ah! That's it!
Let's use that!
But what?
Time TV~!
I see.
You'll use Time TV to see what happened exactly.
Watch carefully.
Oh, it's me!
Ah, I found you, Nobita-san!
I was hiding under there dangerously?
Time TV shows authentic footage.
Ah, it's now me and GIant.
Stop, you jerk!
Stop!
Gotta run!
How reckless of you to do that, Nobita-kun!
I absolutely had no idea!
GIant hadn't got into an accident yet.
But what about that girl's doll?
Let's forward a little ahead.
Ah, be careful, little girl.
My doll fell on the road.
Oh, big brother will pick it for you!
Oh no!
What happened?
Are you hurt, kid?
I see. So that's what really happened.
So Nobita caused this accident.
D-Doraemon!
Nobita-kun, let's go apologize to the little girl.
Yes, we should, Nobita-kun.
Yuki-chan, stop crying!
But my doll has been torn.
Mum will get you a new one, so please...
No, I need Rumi-chan stitched.
Now that's a problem.
Oh my, huh?
Who are you two?
Doctor for your daughter's doll, Auntie.
Really?
We'll treat Rumi-chan.
Doraemon...!
Healing Megaphone!
I'll now heal it.
Yay! Rumi-chan!
I'm hungry!
Mummy, Rumi-chan spoke to me...
I'm glad.
Oh, you crashed into her yesterday?
Sorry, I didn't see her.
No, it's my fault.
I forgot to hold her hands and she held onto her doll..
Mum, let's visit the boy who tried to give me back my doll, in the hospital.
Sure, he must be missing you.
Let's go tomorrow.
Well...
Sign: Limit the Speed!
Oh, you saw the events using Time TV?
It was very uncool of me!
Not really. You tried your best to retrieve the doll.
You think?
Sorry, it's all my fault.
Not really. It's my fault!
We should not have fought.
How are you feeling now?
Great!
Here, I've brought you a cake.
Thanks mister.
It's good to get hurt in a while, actually.
You'll get better if you eat the cake.
Be careful from now on.
Let's conduct an experiment after you've been released.
An experiment?
Are you ready? Here I come!
Stop!
It hit, but...
You can't easily put brake in the vehicle.
If it was a little early, it'd have been burst.
No way...!
Doraemon, do you have a gadget that ensues one's safety?
Of course, I don't have such a gadget!
You all have to follow the traffic etiquette so that you can be safe.
Indeed.
Yup.
I'm off to school!
Oh, Giant!
You're ok, now?
Yup.
Hey, Nobita. Let's switch our places.
Sure.
Suneo, thanks for carrying me.
My butt hurts.
Giant, didn't your right leg got hurt?
You're such a jerk!
Giant!
Hold it, you jerk!
Wait, you two!
i'm glad that all of you are properly following the traffic rules.
The End
RAW by: Ko-FI.me/Femboyfilms
Subtitles by: Ko-FI.me/OrangeFlash